뭐해?
-What are you doing?
-I reorganized the fridge.
냉장고 정리
See? Bottom shelf,
meats and dairy.
제일 밑에 있는 선반은
고기와 유제품
Middle shelf, fruits and vegetables.
중간 선반은 과일과 야채
And top shelf, expired products.
맨 위에는
유통기한 지난 식품
Why are you doing this?
- 왜 이러는 거야?
- 따분해서 미치겠다
Because I'm bored out of my mind.
I've already been to the bank,
post office and dry cleaners.
은행이랑 우체국
세탁소에도 다녀왔어
그건 일주일치 일이야
Dude, you just described
seven days' worth of stuff.
Spread it out a little.
Haven't you ever been unemployed?
적당히 배분을 해야지
실업자 돼본 적 없어?
난 실업자 아냐
잠깐 안식 중이라고
I'm not unemployed.
I'm on sabbatical.
내 앞에서 종교 얘기
들먹거리지 마
Hey, don't get religious
on me, okay?
그런 처지가 되면
좀 쉴 줄도 알아야지
A guy in your position needs to be
better at relaxing.
저 안락의자를 왜 들여놨겠어
That's why we have comfortable chairs.
Here, sit down.
자, 여기 앉아
Ready? Watch.
됐지? 잘 봐
And then....
그리고...
-So, what? We just sit?
-Oh, no, no.
- 그냥 이렇게 앉아있어?
- 아니지
We're not gonna just sit.
Watch.
앉아만 있는 게 아냐
이걸 봐
-Hello, Chandler Bing.
-Hello, Mr. Bing.
챈들러 빙입니다
안녕, 미스터 빙
I love you.
당신을 사랑해요
All right, whoever this is,
stop calling me!
누군지 모르지만 전화 그만하쇼
벌써 6개월 째야
이게 재미있나?
It's been 6 months!
It's not funny!
난 당신이 보여요
I can see you, Mr. Bing.
새 옷을 입으니까
너무 섹시해요
You look sexy in your new suit.
제발 날 그냥 내버려둬
Leave me alone!
For the love of God, leave me alone!
이제 수요일이야
And that's Wednesday.
The One with
The lnappropriate Sister
Hey, you guys! Guess what?
얘들아, 맞혀 봐
The British are coming?
영국이 쳐들어오나?
Oh, you and your ways.
너도 참 못 말리겠다
Since it's Christmas,
I'm going to be collecting donations.
크리스마스잖아
모금운동에 참여하려고
종은 벌써 챙겼고
냄비만 준비하면 돼
I have my bell
and later on I get my bucket.
그래, 사람들에게
기쁨을 나눠줄 거야
I'll be spreading joy
to the people.
작년에도 나눠줬지만
그걸로는 부족했지
Last year I spread a little joy,
but not enough.
올해는 도시 전체를
상대로 할 거야
So this year I'm doing the whole city.
고등학교 때 그런 걸
하던 애가 있었는데
I knew a girl in high school who
did that. She was very popular.
인기 좋았지
이상하다, 요즘 너
챈들러처럼 말해
It's weird, you're starting to sound
a lot like Chandler lately.
- 그럴 리가 있나
That is so not true.
So, Phoebe, where are you
doing your bell-ringing?
피비, 어디 가서
종을 울릴 건데?
자리가 너무 좋아
메이시 백화점 옆
They gave me a great spot
right by Macy's.
They never give a good spot
to a rookie...
신참한테 그런 자리
떨어지기가 힘든데
...but I'm the only one who can say
"Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
'메리 크리스마스'를 25개 국어로
말하는 사람은 나밖에 없었거든
I lied!
거짓말이지만
Oh, my God. Here's Danny.
어머, 대니 들어왔다
잘 봐두라고
Just watch this.
봤지?
See? Still pretending
he's not interested.
여전히 관심 없는 척이야
He's coming over.
Pretend we've forgotten who he is.
온다, 모른 척해
모르는 사람이야
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, Danny.
- 반가워요
- 어서 와요
Oh, Danny! Hey!
오, 대니
왔군요
You know Rachel. She's nice.
She's not bad to look at, right?
대니?
레이첼 알죠? 착하고
외모도 이만하면 됐고
Thanks, Mon.
고맙다
Of course.
물론이죠
Do you want to go out
on a date with her?
- 데이트하고 싶지 않아요?
- 모니카!
Absolutely. Is Friday okay?
그럼요, 금요일 괜찮아요?
금요일 좋아요
기대가 크네요
Friday is perfect.
She can't wait.
On the date, I'll be able
to talk to her directly?
데이트할 때는 직접
얘기하고 싶군요
그럼 금요일에 봐요
See you Friday.
이게 대체 뭐야?
Okay, what the hell was that?
You know what? Don't answer me.
아니, 대답하지 마
I have a date with Danny!
나 대니랑 데이트한다
4시 30분이면
점심시간 끝났군
All right, it's 4:30,
I guess my lunch break is over.
너희들은 뭐할 거야?
-What are you guys gonna do?
-lf you're going back to work...
너 일하러 가면 집에서
전화나 몇 통 해야겠다
...I'll probably just hang out.
You know, make some calls.
그래
How could I not get the part?
왜 저는 안 되죠?
The play was about a 29-year-old
ltalian actor from Queens!
퀸스 출신의 이태리 배우가
주인공인데
탈리아 샤이어가
갑자기 시간이 난대
Well, Talia Shire
suddenly became available.
She's a woman!
여자잖아요
What can I say? She nailed it!
난들 어떡하나
딱 찍었는 걸
- 좋아요, 다른 건 없나요?
- 이번에도 거절하겠지만...
Is there anything else?
You'll just say no again, but...
...gay porn?
게이 포르노?
Happy holidays!
행복한 연말 맞으세요
'펠리츠 나비다드'
Feliz Navidad!
Allo and Merry Christmas!
'알로', 메리 크리스마스
Oh, thank you, sir!
Here's some joy.
감사합니다
기쁨 가져가세요
- 안녕, 피비?
- 왔어?
-How's it going?
-It's going okay.
- 잘 돼가?
- 그런 대로
다행이네
여기, 나도 좀 낼게
Good. Let me help you out.
고맙다
Oh, thanks!
Is that a new suede jacket?
It looks really expensive.
그 스웨이드 재킷
되게 비싸 보인다
Yeah. I guess.
그래... 조금
Just get your nails done?
손톱도 손질했니?
Yes, Phoebe, but this
is all I have, okay?
가진 건 이게 다야
좋아, 고마워
여기 기쁨도 가져가
Thanks. Happy holidays!
Here's your joy.
고마워
Thank you! Happy holidays and
Wait.
감사합니다
행복한 연말 맞으세요
잠깐, 꺼내면 안 돼요
-You can't take money out.
-I'm making change for the bus.
거슬러 가려고요
버스 타야 돼요
불우한 이웃을
돕기 위한 돈인데
Can't you leave the
dollar for the poor?
내가 불우한 이웃이오
버스 타야 된다니까
I'm poor.
I gotta take the bus.
Okay, season's greetings and everything,
but still
복 받으세요, 하지만...
됐수다, 아가씨
Bite me, blondie!
기쁨 말고 이것도 가져가라
I'm going to give him
something besides joy. Just
I can't believe
I didn't get that part.
완벽한 배역인데
그걸 놓치다니
I'm sorry, man.
유감이다
What you should do...
이건 어떨까?
스스로 길을 개척하는 거야
...is make something happen
for yourself.
You know, like write a play.
가령 희곡을 쓴다든지
영화대본도 좋고
Or a movie. What about those
Good Will Hunting guys?
'굿 윌 헌팅'처럼
현실적으로 생각해라
Be realistic, you know?
If I did write something...
내가 글을 쓰면
그 친구들을 어떻게 섭외하냐?
...what are the chances I could
get those guys to star in it?
Wait a second.
I could star in it!
- 내가 출연하면 되겠네
- 아무렴!
Or that.
I can't write.
I mean, I'm an actor.
난 글 못 써
배우가 연기나 할 줄 알았지
작가라니, 어디 볼까?
I could act like a writer. Here....
보여? 꽝이야
But see? Nada.
그쪽은 아는 것도 없고
I don't have the discipline
that it takes. I can't do it.
난 못해
I'll help you.
내가 도와줄게, 그래
Yeah. I'll make up a schedule
and make sure you stick to it.
계획표를 짤 테니까
잘 따라오기나 해
Plus, it'll give me something to do.
난 소일거리도 생기고
You'd do that for me?
Thanks.
정말 그래줄래?
- 그럼
- 고맙다
We'll start slow. All you have
to come up with tonight...
좋아, 시작은 천천히
오늘밤엔 주연들의
이름만 정하는 거야
...is the name
of your main character.
-Done.
-And it can't be Joey.
- 끝났어
- 조이는 안 돼
-It's not.
-Or Joseph.
- 아냐
- 조셉도
왔어?
What's up?
왜 그래?
I just saw Danny on the subway
with a girl...
대니가 어떤 여자랑
전철 타는 걸 봤는데
...and he had his arm
around her.
- 어깨에 팔을 두르고 있더라
- 어쩌니
Honey, I'm sorry.
You should be.
This is all your fault.
미안하겠지
다 네 잘못이니까
You meddled in our relationship!
우리 사이에 끼어들었어
You had no relationship!
아무 사이도 아니잖아
난 내가 할 일을 한 거고
계획대로 잘되고 있었어
But I was doing my thing
and everything...
...was going according to the plan!
Oh, God, stop with the plan!
그 계획 좀 집어치워라
So what if you saw him
with a girl?
여자랑 같이 있는 게
뭐 대수라고, 별 거 아냐
That doesn't mean anything.
You'll go out with Danny and be
so charming he'll forget all about...
대니는 너와 데이트 약속했잖아
너한테 반해서 그 멍청한
지하철 여자는 잊을 거야
...that stupid subway girl.
She was kind of stupid.
멍청해 보이긴 하더라
You're right.
I'm just going to go on the date.
맞아
그래, 데이트하는 거야
I'm just going to go on the date.
That is the new plan.
나가서 만나겠어
그게 새로운 계획이야
Hurry!
빨리!
-How do you spell "suspicious"?
-Why?
'의심하다'의 철자가 뭐지?
왜?
주인공이 뭘 의심하게 되거든
I think this character is going
to be suspicious about stuff.
그렇지!
Chandler Bing, seven!
Chandler Bing, zero!
챈들러 빙, 7점
챈들러 빙, 0점
You're driving me crazy with that.
- 그것 때문에 미치겠다
- 알았어, 그만 할게
-I'll stop.
-Don't stop.
그게 아니라 그릇을 멀리 둬
로스는 더 잘해
Move the bowl further away.
Ross could make that shot.
Well, you suck. But at least you suck
at a man's game now.
망했지만 적어도
남자다운 게임을 한 거야
-Want to play?
-I can't play games.
너도 할래?
그럴 시간 없다
로스가 곧 올 거야
Ross'll be home soon. I have to write
five pages to stick to his schedule.
계획표에 따라서
다섯 장을 써야 돼
30분만 놀면 로스 오기 전에
마칠 수 있잖아
So play for 30 minutes,
then write until he gets home.
All right.
좋아
But listen, what do you say we...
난이도를 약간
높이는 게 어떨까?
...crank it up a notch?
I'm intrigued.
원하던 바올시다
All right. All we need
is a little lighter fluid.
좋아, 불붙일 게 필요해
But be careful.
I want our security deposit back.
조심해, 보증금
돌려 받고 싶으면
We said goodbye to that
when we invented hammer darts.
그건 우리가 '해머 다트'
만들었을 때 날아갔잖아
Do you even remember which part
of the wall is not spackle?
- 어디가 안 뚫렸는지 알아?
- 그래, 여기야
Thank you! Happy holiday.
감사합니다
행복한 명절 맞으세요
No, that's trash, young lady.
You can't
쓰레기잖아요, 아가씨
그럼 안 되죠, 이봐요
Stop that young lady!
She donated trash!
저 아가씨 잡아요!
쓰레기를 기부했어요!
이봐요!
The charity's on fire!
자선냄비 불났네!
Help!
Thank you. I need that!
도와줘요, 잘됐다
마침 필요했는데
What is this?
이게 뭐죠?
It's 9:00 in the morning!
아침 9시예요
All right. "A room.
좋아, 실내
남자 들어온다
의심하는 듯하다
A man enters. He looks suspicious."
That's it?
이게 다야?
You're supposed to
have five pages done by now...
다섯 장 써놓으라고 했잖아
짜릿한 사건 하나 포함해서
...including an exciting incident.
이건 다 뭐야?
파이어볼 공식 규칙집?
What is all this?
"The Official Rulebook of Fireball."
That's the game we played.
우리가 하던 게임이야
It's great. You take a
tennis ball, a bowl and lighter
맞아, 테니스공이랑...
그릇, 불붙이는... 어어?
This is helping your career?
You wanted to be an actor.
이게 경력에 보탬이 돼?
배우가 되고 싶다더니
정신 나간 법정 게임 개발할래?
Not the creator of
"Crazy Lawsuit Game."
You're right.
I'll get back to work.
그래, 네 말이 맞다
공부해야지
Shame on you! You should know better!
Joey needs to work.
너도 알면서 그러는 거 아냐
조이는 공부를 해야 돼
Now come on.
어서 해!
안 돼, 다섯 장
채우기 전엔 못 줘
You can have this back
when the five pages are done.
-I had a nice time tonight.
-So did l.
오늘 정말 즐거웠어요
나두요
I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
모니카가 기특한 일했네요
I'd love to ask you in,
but my sister's visiting.
함께 들어갔으면 좋겠지만
여동생이 소파에서
자고 있을 것 같아서
-I think she's asleep on the couch.
-Your sister?
여동생?
Your sister's asleep on the couch?
여동생이 소파에서 자요?
I saw you with her on the subway
and now she's asleep on the couch!
전철에서 여동생 봤는데
이제 소파에서 자는구나
세상에
-I thought I heard you.
-Hey, great, you're up.
- 오빠인 줄 알았어
- 그래, 일어났구나
내 동생 크리스타예요
이쪽은 레이첼이야
Rachel, my sister Krista.
Nice to meet you.
- 안녕
- 반가워요
I wish you'd warned me.
I'd have fixed myself up.
손님 온다고 말하지
준비라도 할 텐데
-Like it would help.
-You are so bad.
- 그럼 뭐 달라지나?
- 오빠 나빠
-You are.
- 네가 나빠
- 오빠가
-You are.
-You are!
- 네가
- 오빠가
You are so dead.
혼날 줄 알아
I'm gonna get you.
Come here!
잡으러 간다
이리 와
이리 와, 어서
만나서 반가웠어요
It's very nice to meet you.
Nobody!
Nobody respects the bucket!
도대체 냄비에 대한
존경심들이 없어
You wouldn't believe
what people put in here!
여기다 뭘 넣었는지 알아?
봐, 이게 쓰레기통으로
보이니?
Does this look like a
garbage can to you?
- 아니
- 그럼 재떨이 같아?
Does it look like an ashtray?
- 아니
- 소변기 같아?
Does it look like a urinal?
-So you going back out there?
-Yeah, but I won't take any more crap.
- 그래서 다시 나갈 거야?
- 그래
하지만 나도 이젠 못 참아
착한 자선냄비는 끝났어
No more Mrs. Nice Bucket.
잘 생각했다, 거리에서
쌓은 터프함을 보여줘
Good. You're tough.
You lived on the street.
거리의 피비로 돌아가겠어
I'll go back to being
Street Phoebe.
맞아
But not totally back. Street Phoebe
wouldn't be friends with you guys.
그래도 완전히 돌아갈 순 없지
그럼 너희랑 못 어울리니까
얘들아
Can I ask you guys something?
- 뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 그래
I don't have brothers, so I don't know,
but did you guys wrestle?
난 오빠가 없어서 모르겠는데
- 혹시 너희들도 레슬링했니?
- 그럼
-Oh, yeah.
-All the time.
틈만 나면
In fact, I was undefeated.
사실 난 진 적이 없어
Well, you weighed 200 pounds.
그때 넌 90Kg이었어
Still, I was quick as a cat.
그래도 고양이처럼 민첩했지
I met Danny's sister yesterday.
어제 대니 여동생을 만났는데
내가 전철에서 봤던 그 여자
-That was the girl on the subway.
-You're kidding.
- 그렇구나
- 그런데 두 사람...
They were very, you know...
...wrestle-y.
레슬링을 좋아하더라
물론 정상이겠지?
But I guess that's normal?
We don't wrestle now.
우린 지금 레슬링 안 해
이젠 내 상대가 안 되지
Not since I got too
strong for you.
Too strong for me?
- 상대가 안 돼?
- 그럼
You wanna go right now?
한번 해볼까?
I'll take you right now, buddy!
You wanna go?
지금도 문제없어
붙어볼 테야?
Oh, fine.
좋지
Ready?
준비?
Wrestle!
시작!
Okay, you know what?
저기...
Actually, that helps a lot.
Thanks.
도움이 많이 됐다, 고마워
Let's go!
The puck drops in 20 minutes!
20분 후에 게임 시작인데
뭐 하는 거야, 조이
Joey's not going.
조이는 못 가
I didn't finish my five pages.
아직 다섯 장 못 채웠다
Finish them tomorrow.
내일 끝내면 되잖아
내일은 어제 걸
수정해야 하니까
Tomorrow he's redoing
yesterday's pages.
Yesterday's pages
did not reflect my best work.
어제 건 약간 수준 미달이었어
Cut him some slack. If he relaxes,
he'll get some work done.
숨 좀 돌리는 게 어때?
쉬면 더 잘할 수도 있잖아
I think he's been relaxing enough,
thanks to you...
충분히 쉬었어, 너하고...
파이어볼 덕분에
...and Fireball.
If you think Fireball's relaxing,
you've never played.
파이어볼 하면서 쉬어?
역시 안 해봐서 몰라
You're doing this
because you're bored.
너 지금 따분하니까
조이한테 이러는 거지?
It's not his fault
you're unemployed.
백수 된 게 조이 잘못이냐?
난 백수가 아냐
안식 중이라고
I am not unemployed.
I'm on sabbatical!
Guys, don't fight.
싸우지들 마라
내가 조이의 친구이기
때문에 이러는 거야
And I'm doing this because
I am Joey's friend.
If you were a friend,
you'd be doing the same.
너도 좋은 친구라면
그렇게 할 거야
바보짓하면 좋은 친구가
되는 건가?
So being a friend means
being a jerk?
If it does, then you're
an amazing friend of mine.
그렇다면 넌 훌륭한
내 친구지
다정하게 파이어볼로
결판내는 게 어때?
Let's settle this
over a game of Fireball.
-I'll unhook the smoke detectors.
-Let's settle this right now.
- 화재경보기는 내가 손볼게
- 당장 결판내자
어때, 이제 아무도
경기장에 못 가
There. Now no one's going
to the game.
내 돈 주고 산 거야
-I paid for those!
-You said you would, but you didn't.
아니지, 말은 그렇게
했지만 그런 적 없어
Oh, yeah.
그래
We finally get
to the top of the mountain...
결국 정상에 올라갔죠
...and airhead here
forgets the camera.
그런데 이 바보가
카메라를 놓고 온 거예요
The same thing
happened to me one time.
나도 그런 경험이 있죠
When did that happen to you?
언제 그런 경험을 하셨나?
Remember? We were jogging
and saw that bird.
우리 공원에서 조깅하다
예쁜 새를 보고
I wanted to take a picture,
but I didn't have my camera.
사진을 찍으려고 했더니
카메라가 없었잖아
배달부 쫓아간 건
조깅이 아냐
Chasing the churro
guy is not jogging.
Oh, this is so good.
You have got to try it.
정말 맛있다
오빠도 먹어봐
-Damn. I got it on my pants.
-Here, I'll get it.
이런, 바지에 묻었네
자, 내가 닦아줄게
We better take them off
or the stain will set.
얼룩지기 전에 올라가서 벗어
- 데이트할 때 입을 거였는데
- 멋지네요
-I want to wear them tonight.
-Oh, great.
잘 가요, 맙소사
Okay, bye. Oh, my God!
-That was unbelievable.
-See? I told you.
- 이럴 수도 있니?
- 내가 말했잖아
- 안됐다, 레이첼
- 진짜 남매지간 맞아?
Yeah. Sorry.
I don't believe they're
brother and sister.
They're brother and sister?!
둘이 남매야?
I guess you'll have to cancel your date.
- 데이트 취소해라
- 재들 엄마한테 연락하고
And call their mother.
우린 소변기가 아니에요
Wait a minute. Open your hand.
Let me take a look.
잠깐, 손 좀 벌려보세요
Quarter, dime. Lint?
Not interested in that.
25센트, 10센트, 실밥?
이런 건 관심 없어요
What's this?
A Canadian coin?
이건 캐나다 동전이네?
저리 가세요!
Get out of here!
No drinks near the bucket.
자선냄비 근처에서
음료수는 안 돼요
Set it down there and then
you can make a contribution.
저기다 두고 돈 넣으세요
You can leave the "hurt bunny"
look over there too.
그 떫은 표정도 두고 오시죠
Hi, Bob.
안녕, 밥
I thought I told you
to get out of here!
저리 가라고 했잖아요!
Phoebe, we've been
getting complaints.
피비, 항의가 많이 들어와서
좀 한적한 데로 옮겨야겠어요
We're moving you to a
less high-profile spot.
네?
- 여긴 진저가 맡을 거예요
- 애송이가 여길 어떻게
-Ginger's taking this corner.
-That chick can't handle my corner.
Look, either you leave
or we remove you.
옮기기 싫으면
그만두는 수밖에요
Fine.
알았어요
I'll give you one pointer.
Look out for that bitch.
미리 충고하는데
저 할망구 조심해요
-I thought we said 7.
-You know what? Let's skip it.
안녕, 레이첼
7시 아닌가요?
네, 그건 아는데
취소하려고요
What? Why?
네? 왜요?
You and your sister seem to have
a very special bond
여동생과 아주
특별한 관계 같더군요
Oh, great.
That "special bond" again.
멋지군, 그 특별한
관계 또 나왔네
Why do women have a problem
with my being close to my sister?
여동생과 친한 게
무슨 죄라도 되나요?
저기, 내 말 들어봐요
내막은 잘 모르지만...
-I don't know, but
-Do you have brothers?
혹시 오빠 있어요?
No, I have two sisters. But one
has a very masculine energy.
아뇨, 언니만 둘이에요
하지만 그 중 하나는
남자나 다름없죠
-Are you close?
-No. They're not very nice people.
- 언니들이랑 친한 가요?
- 아뇨, 못된 애들이라
들어봐요
I like you.
I think this could go somewhere.
난 당신이 정말 좋아요
잘될 것 같은데
So I'm close to my family.
Don't let it stand in our way.
식구들과 가까운 게
문제가 되나요?
Well, I don't know....
글쎄, 모르겠어요
그렇게 말한다면...
When you put it that way
Danny? Hurry up.
The bath's getting cold.
오빠, 빨리 와
목욕물 식는다
왜요?
I'll see you later.
다음에 봐요
There's some kids
playing in the street.
있었구나
애들이 길에서 노는데
Want to go give them a project,
ruin their day?
가서 숙제 내주고
기분 잡쳐 놔라
If they have a ball,
you could stick razors in it...
공을 갖고 놀면 면도날로
자르고 새 게임을 가르쳐 줘
...and teach them a new game:
"Gonna-Need-Stitches Ball."
공 꿰매기 놀이
Hey, guys! I was at the library.
I already finished my five pages.
얘들아, 아침에 도서관에서
오늘 거 다섯 장 끝냈다
Now we can go
to the Ranger game last night!
잘했네, 그럼 어젯밤
레인저 게임에 가자
그 티켓은 로스가 찢어버렸잖아
No, dude.
Ross tore up the tickets.
I guess without so many distractions
it's easier for you to focus?
주위에 유혹이 별로 없다면
집중하기가 훨씬 쉽겠지?
Also without somebody breathing
down your neck all the livelong day!
목덜미에 거친 숨 몰아쉬는
인간도 없어야지, 하루 종일!
The important thing is, I finished it.
And I think it's really good.
어쨌든 끝낸 게 중요하잖아
난 괜찮은 거 같은데
직접 들어보면 더 좋겠어
But it would help if I could hear it.
Would you guys read it for me?
너희들이 읽어줄래?
-Yeah, all right.
-All right.
- 그래
- 좋아
전형적인 뉴욕의 아파트
두 남자의 대화, 로스?
"It's a typical New York apartment.
Two guys are hanging out."
"Hey, man."
안녕?
"What is up?"
왜 그래?
"About yesterday.
I was really wrong. I am sorry."
어제 일 말인데
내가 잘못했어, 미안해
"No, it was me. I'm sorry.
I overreacted."
아냐, 나 때문이지
미안해, 내가 지나쳤어
"Maybe it was both of us.
But we had our best friend's inter
둘 다 잘못했겠지만
우리 가슴엔 따스한...
But we had our best friend's
interest at heart."
따스한 우정이 흐르고 있어
"Could I be more sorry?"
이 미안한 맘을
어떻게 표현하지?
"l don't know. I am one sorry...
글쎄, 나야말로 못된...
...polontologist."
'구생물학자'야
All right, Joey, we get it.
그래, 알아들었어
-I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry too.
- 미안하다
- 나도 미안해
아냐, 계속 읽어
중요한 대목이 남았어
Keep reading.
The good part's coming up.
"l am sorry, Chandler."
미안하다, 챈들러
"l am sorry, Ross."
내가 미안해, 로스
"A handsome man enters."
멋진 남자 들어온다
얘들아
"l don't know what you're talking
about, but I'd like to thank you both.
무슨 얘길 했는지 모르지만
두 사람 다 정말 고마워
You. You wouldn't let me
give up on myself.
넌 나한테 힘을 줬고
그리고 넌...
And you.
You co-created Fireball."
나랑 파이어볼을 만들어냈잖아
"The End."
끝!
This took you all day?
이걸 하루 종일 썼냐?
아니, 이건 5분 걸렸어
No, this took five minutes.
I spent the rest of the day coming up
with new Ultimate Fireball!
여태까지 새 게임을 만들었지
'최후의 파이어볼'
It's a typical New York apartment.
Two girls are just hanging out. Go.
전형적인 뉴욕의 아파트
두 여자의 대화
-"Hi, how are you doing, Kelly?"
-"I'm doing just fine.
요즘 어때, 켈리?
난 좋아
God, Tiffany, you smell so great."
티파니, 너한테서
진짜 좋은 냄새난다
"It's my new perfume.
새로 산 향수거든
가까이 와서 잘 맡아봐
Why don't you come closer where
you can really appreciate it?"
-Joey, you are sick.
-This is disgusting.
- 조이, 너 정말 심하다
- 메스껍다
I'm not reading this.
- 읽기 싫어
- 정말 못 말려
Wait, wait, wait!
The handsome man was about to enter!
기다려, 멋진 남자가
들어올 순간이야